https://www.desertpipes.org/privacy-policy

Contact Us
Privacy PolicyPhoenix Desert Pipes is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to Phoenix Desert Pipes website and governs data collection and usage at this site. Personal information of all users is collected, used, and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy. Who We AreOur website address is: https://www.desertpipes.org. What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect ItPhoenix Desert Pipes does not collect any information except for that entered by into the contact form by any individual who makes contact with us (see the next section on Contact Forms), and information as entered on any workshop registration form. We will on occasion share names and emails with other recorder organizations, but not without the express permission of our members. We also do not share your information with anyone else, no exceptions.You may request, in writing or by email, at any time for all personal information to be removed fromWe are not responsible for the privacy policies of any sites to which our site may provide links or otherwise identify. Phoenix Desert Pipes encourages you to review the privacy statements of such websites so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. Contact FormsThe contact form on our website is through Jotform. The information captured is exactly what is on the form: name, email, and message sent. No other information is collected. This information is stored at JotForm indefinitely and can be deleted any time upon your request. This information is never used for any purpose other than contacting Phoenix Desert Pipes and is used only for dissemination of information from Phoenix Desert Pipes or other recorder organizations. Your information will never be sold or given to anyone for any other purpose. Click here for JotForms’ compliance policy.
CookiesAs of the time of this revision, Phoenix Desert Pipes does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software. Cookies are not enabled on this website. Embedded Content from Other WebsitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website. As previously stated, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of any sites to which our site may provide links or otherwise identify. Phoenix Desert Pipes encourages you to review the privacy statements of such websites so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. Website AnalyticsThe Phoenix Desert Pipes website uses Google Analytics for general website tracking statistics. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. You should review their Privacy Policy and contact them directly if you have questions. If you do not want any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, visit the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool. Security of Your Personal InformationPhoenix Desert Pipes is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. This website, https://www.desertpipes.org, is secured by an SSL (Secure Socket Layer) digital certificate. We store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access.
What Rights You Have Over Your DataYou can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. Changes to This StatementPhoenix Desert Pipes will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect website visitor feedback and future compliance regulation changes. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Phoenix Desert Pipes will use your personal information, Phoenix Desert Pipes will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Phoenix Desert Pipes encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Phoenix Desert Pipes is protecting your information. Conditions of UseBy using the pages in this site, the Phoenix Desert Pipes website, you agree to our terms of use. If you do not agree, please leave our site and look elsewhere for your recorder information. We encourage you to review the following information carefully. These terms may be changed or updated from time to time. TrademarksAny trademarks used on our site are owned exclusively by their owners. The use of these trademarks and trade dress is governed by law, and permission must be obtained from the owners prior to use, in accordance with US and international law. CopyrightAll content on this website is the exclusive property of Phoenix Desert Pipes or other copyright owners. Said content includes text, graphics, logos, icons, images, audio and video clips, digital downloads, and software. Our content is protected by United States and international copyright laws and we reserve all rights contained therein. In case of dispute or infringement, we will rigorously defend our rights to this material.Fair use: We grant you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited right to access, view, use, display and print information on this site for your personal, informational, noncommercial use only. Please share information from our website with anyone who may be interested subject to the above fair use terms. See License and Site Access section for additional terms. Licenses and Site AccessPhoenix Desert Pipes grants you (the user) fair use access to make personal use of this website. This license does not include the right to download any material (other than routine page caching), modify any material, or any portion thereof, without the express written consent of Phoenix Desert Pipes, except for the Fair Use authorized above. This license excludes the download or collection of logos, product descriptions, pricing, text, graphics, audio and video clips, and/or copying account information, except for Fair Use.This website or any portion of this website may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written permission of Phoenix Desert Pipes. You are prohibited from using meta tags or any other hidden text utilizing Phoenix Desert Pipes’ name or trademarks without the express written consent of Phoenix Desert Pipes. Any unauthorized use of this websites voids the fair use permission granted by Phoenix Desert Pipes. Contact InformationIf you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation please contact us. We may ask you to provide proof of identity before we show you this personal information so we can prevent unauthorized access.Phoenix Desert PipesEmail: info@desertpipes.org. Revised 5/17/2020
Copyright © 2020 Phoenix Desert Pipes. All Rights Reserved. Click here for our Privacy Policy.
